TRI KHUONG QUAN

JAVA(INTERN)



Profile

After returning home from two years of studying abroad in Japan, I am currently honing my skills as a developer, especially in game production. This adventure has allowed me to explore multiple programming languages such as Java, C++, C#, and Python. I've delved not only into their syntax but also into their distinct characteristics and nuances, which have added a vibrant and diverse palette to my coding journey.

Education

2017 - 2019 Tokyo World Japanese Language School

Language School, Tokyo

A good experience to learn about the culture

of Japan.

2021 - 2024 Greenwich University

University, Ho Chi Minh

Currently learning and experiencing international working culture from Greenwich.

Experience

2017 - 2019 Izakaya restaurant

Part-timer, Tokyo

Tried out all of the position, from main chief to dish washer.

2021 - 2024 Greenwich university

Student, Ho Chi Minh city

Experience multiple realistic project from front end static web, to back end dynamic web, including handling platform and database.

Skills

Can use multiple OOP

- languages: Java, C++, C#, python.
- Can use English and Japanese
- Team work
- **✓** Work under pressure
- Communication
- **✓** Time management
- Self learning

Contact

- A Binh Tan, Ho Chi Minh
- 0332565790
- in www.linkedin.com/in/trikhuong-quan-b5260416b
- https://github.com/Tristory? tab=repositories

Additional activities

- Working as volunteer in a distribute event.
- F Running a personal RPG project using unity.

Career Objective

Short: Gaining experience as a developer. In both aspects of soft skill and hard skill. Explore how to make product in more professional way.

Long: Gaming has long been an underrated field, their application Gaming has long been an underrated field, their application has never been too far from the entertainment industry, which is a huge waste of potential. Time and time again, multiple research papers have come out to prove the undeniable stimulus effect of gaming, which demands minimal physical effect. I want to explore such possibilities and push them further.

Certificate

IELTS(2021)



6.5 overall, and 8.0 for reading



JLPT(2018)